NELSON DALY

nelson.daly@outlook.com | nelsond.tech

About Me

An inquisitive and proactive frontend developer, with strong problem-solving skills and experience delivering results in a fast-paced environment. Able to communicate effectively with all levels of seniority and degrees of technical understanding.

Skills

TypeScript (JavaScript) | Angular 13 | HTML5 | CSS3 | Java (basic knowledge)

Experience

Portfolio Web App (nelsond.tech/this.app)

• Built a Single-Page Application in the style of a code editor, using Angular 13, with a resizable preview section showcasing live demonstrations of all additional projects created.

Issue Tracker App (nelsond.tech/issuetracker.app)

• Designed and developed an embedded CRUD web application, featuring vanilla TypeScript chart visualizations.

Scientific Calculator App (nelsond.tech/scicalculator.app)

• Created an emulation of Casio fx-991MS. Implemented 80% functionality for the minimum viable product.

Local Weather Forecast App (nelsond.tech/localweather.app)

• Built a live weather forecast widget, consuming JSON data from a third-party RESTful API.

Other Experience

Freelance

Audio Engineer

2021 - Present

• Partnering with clients to achieve sonically cohesive productions, at industry-standard loudness levels.

Goldman Sachs

Business Management Support – Engineering Division

2013 - 2021

• Assisted cross-region Senior Leadership teams with strategic projects, initiatives and business management activities. Served as the primary administrative contact for all regional staff within numerous Business Units.

Education

University of Pennsylvania

2020 - 2021

- Certificate in SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript
- Certificate in SD2x: Data Structures and Software Design
- Certificate in SD1x: Software Development Fundamentals

Microsoft 2020

- Certificate in DEV262x: Logic and Computational Thinking
- Certificate in DAT201x: Querying Data with Transact-SQL

British Academy of New Music

2011 - 2013

• Level 3 RSL Extended Diploma for Music Technology